topb2c.com 2014-04-04

# Privacy Notice :

﻿ 

Due to the nature of our website and in an effort to improve your shopping experience, topb2c.com does collect personally identifiable information as well as log aggregate shopping information. We recognize we must maintain and use customer information responsibly. **We respect your privacy and will never sell your information to third parties.**

**What personal information is collected and how is it used?**  
Personal information is considered any information that is specific to you, such as your name, email address, credit card information, etc. In order to make a purchase or receive topb2c.com's newsletter, users must enter their personal information.

When you make a purchase, we require that you provide your shipping and billing address, phone number and credit card information (if paying by credit card). This information is stored in a secure database, only accessible to select employees with access rights to this information. topb2c.com protects your online order information using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. 

Additionally, topb2c.com logs your Internet Protocol Address (IP). An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when browsing the Internet. Information from IP addresses is used for system administration, to examine overall traffic trends, troubleshooting, etc. This information is used only in the aggregate form. IP addresses are not linked to any PII, meaning that your session on our site is tracked, but will not be linked to any personal information.

**How secure is my personal information?**  
Your information is secure with topb2c.com! Protecting your order information is a priority. topb2c.com uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to insure that all data passed between our server and your web browser remain private and secure.

SSL encrypts your order information to avoid the decoding of that information by anyone other than topb2c.com. To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), this means the SSL is active. You can also double check by looking at your browsers URL. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https".

Some firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In this case, you will not be able to connect to the secure server and must disable your firewall or choose a different method to order.

**Cookies: What are they and how do we use them?**  
A web tracking cookie is a bit of electronic information that a website or web browser can place on your computer's hard drive in order to do specific jobs like remember your preferences or shopping cart contents. Cookies allow web site operators to better customize site visits to the visitor's preferences. The use of cookies has become standard on the Internet and most major websites use them.

topb2c.com uses cookies to help keep track of the products you add to your wishlist and your cart so that we can provide a more convenient shopping experience. Please be assured that we do not use cookies to track any information about other sites you may visit or to collect any additional personal information.

Although most browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your web browser’s preferences to block cookies or notify you whenever you are sent a cookie.

**Protection for Children**  

topb2c.com is not intended for users under the age of 18, and we have no intention of collecting Personal Information from children (i.e., individuals under the age of 13). Where appropriate, we take reasonable measures to inform children not to submit such information to our site or in response to advertisements. If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, your dealings with topb2c.com, or would like to opt-out of receiving communications from us, you can contact us — **[sales@topb2c.com](mailto:sales@topb2c.com)**.
